edventures.com 2019-02-27

# Privacy Policy – PCS Edventures

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the content and services offered by PCS Edventures!, Inc. and any of its affiliates (collectively, “PCS”),  including without limitation the websites at edventures.com, edventureslab.com, and any subdomain thereof and any content and services PCS provides on mobile devices, but excludes content and services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include PCS content or services, or other sites linked from our content or services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

Please read this statement carefully before using or proceeding to access any PCS content or services. Your use of any PCS content or services indicates that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms of Use in effect and to be subject to this policy.

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you visit our site, register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1) To personalize your experience

    (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs, such as to provide you services or content that you have registered for or purchased)

2) To improve our website

   (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

3) To improve customer service

   (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

4) To process transactions

 Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

5) To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features

6) To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into “My Account” and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Security

We take the security of customer information very seriously. Our checkout process is protected by SSL encryption technology. We adhere to the credit card industry’s best practices, which includes displaying the last four digits only of a credit card number when we confirm orders.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions, which establish the terms of use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing your use of our website, at http://edventures-com.myshopify.com/pages/terms-and-conditions 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on November 20, 2015

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

PCS Edventures!, Inc.  
345 Bobwhite Court, Suite 200  
Boise, ID, USA 83706  
Voice: 800.429.3110  
Voice: 208.343.3110  
Fax: 208.343.1321  
Product Information: info@edventures.com  
Customer Support: support@edventures.com
